<!--AUTOGENERATED THROUGH PYSCRIPTS FROM QUEST DOCS-->
<data>
	<copy>
		<prompt_response_0>Chat with Silvermist.</prompt_response_0>
		<prompt_response_1>Chat with Silvermist.</prompt_response_1>
		<prompt_response_2>Chat with Silvermist.</prompt_response_2>
		<prompt_response_3>Chat with Silvermist.</prompt_response_3>
		<prompt_response_4>Chat with Silvermist.</prompt_response_4>
		<prompt_response_5>Chat with Silvermist.</prompt_response_5>
		<prompt_response_6>Chat with Silvermist.</prompt_response_6>
		<prompt_response_7>Chat with Silvermist.</prompt_response_7>
		<prompt_response_8>Chat with Silvermist.</prompt_response_8>
		<prompt_response_9>Chat with Silvermist.</prompt_response_9>
		<response_0_0>I love everything about water! Water drops, water bubbles, the plants that grow around water...</response_0_0>
		<response_0_1>I really like lily pads and cat tails, and especially lotus flowers.</response_0_1>
		<response_0_2>Nothing brightens my day like wearing a lotus flower in my hair. They're so beautiful... they almost make me cry...!</response_0_2>
		<response_1_0>I really like the color blue. It's the color of lakes and rivers and streams.</response_1_0>
		<response_1_1>But I just love ultramarine! That's a really deep blue. It reminds me of the sea!</response_1_1>
		<response_1_2>I always feel so wonderfully relaxed and calm when I see ultramarine. It's like seeing a little drop of the ocean!</response_1_2>
		<response_2_0>You know, I just checked my wardrobe, and all my clothes are awfully BLUE.</response_2_0>
		<response_2_1>Oh well, I guess I just can't get enough Hydrangea Blue and Candy Blue dye!</response_2_1>
		<response_3_0>Have you ever bounced a fishie bubble? It's one of my most FAVORITE things to do!</response_3_0>
		<response_3_1>You have to come visit me at Soapstone Stream some time. We can bounce fishie bubbles together!</response_3_1>
		<response_4_0>Everybody says I'm emotional, but hello? I'm a water-talent! I cry at the drop of a drip!</response_4_0>
		<response_4_1>And I really don't like shouting or yelling. It makes me feel so sad.</response_4_1>
		<response_4_2>Besides, it's hard to say anything nice when you're yelling, right? I'd rather laugh. Bubbling streams laugh all the time!</response_4_2>
		<response_5_0>You may have noticed that it's kinda hard to find Lily Petals in the meadows sometimes.</response_5_0>
		<response_5_1>Well, I'll let you in on a secret...</response_5_1>
		<response_5_2>If you ever need Lily Petals, visit me in Spider Silk Grotto. If you help me collect dewdrops there, I'll share some of my Lily Petals with you!</response_5_2>
		<response_6_0>Oh, I'm glad you're here! I heard a joke and I just have to tell it to you! Why did the whale cross the ocean?</response_6_0>
		<response_6_1>Give up?</response_6_1>
		<response_6_2>To get to the other TIDE!</response_6_2>
		<response_6_3>That's water-talent humor.</response_6_3>
		<response_7_0>You know what I like BEST about being a water-talent? I can... I mean, there's just so much to... and then there's... and, and...</response_7_0>
		<response_7_1>*SIGH* And I can't make up my mind!</response_7_1>
		<response_8_0>Whenever my house decorations start to get boring, I like to brighten things up with something new!</response_8_0>
		<response_8_1>I always find something perfect at Trinket's shop in Treetop Bend!</response_8_1>
		<response_8_2>Remember, "If it's beautiful and useable it must be from Treetop Housewares!"</response_8_2>
		<response_9_0>I'll admit it. I cry a lot. I mean, a LOT.</response_9_0>
		<response_9_1>But I can't help it! I'm a water-talent! All water-talents cry a lot.</response_9_1>
		<response_9_2>It's like we're filled with extra water or something!</response_9_2>
	</copy>
	<storyBoards>
		<storyBoard id="response_0">
			<line >response_0_0</line>
			<line >response_0_1</line>
			<line >response_0_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_1">
			<line >response_1_0</line>
			<line >response_1_1</line>
			<line >response_1_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_2">
			<line >response_2_0</line>
			<line >response_2_1</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_3">
			<line >response_3_0</line>
			<line >response_3_1</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_4">
			<line >response_4_0</line>
			<line >response_4_1</line>
			<line >response_4_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_5">
			<line >response_5_0</line>
			<line >response_5_1</line>
			<line >response_5_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_6">
			<line >response_6_0</line>
			<line >response_6_1</line>
			<line >response_6_2</line>
			<line >response_6_3</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_7">
			<line >response_7_0</line>
			<line >response_7_1</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_8">
			<line >response_8_0</line>
			<line >response_8_1</line>
			<line >response_8_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_9">
			<line >response_9_0</line>
			<line >response_9_1</line>
			<line >response_9_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
	</storyBoards>
	<otherStoryBoards>
	</otherStoryBoards>
</data>