<!--AUTOGENERATED THROUGH PYSCRIPTS FROM QUEST DOCS-->
<data>
	<copy>
		<prompt_response_0>Chat with Iridessa.</prompt_response_0>
		<prompt_response_1>Chat with Iridessa.</prompt_response_1>
		<prompt_response_2>Chat with Iridessa.</prompt_response_2>
		<prompt_response_3>Chat with Iridessa.</prompt_response_3>
		<prompt_response_4>Chat with Iridessa.</prompt_response_4>
		<prompt_response_5>Chat with Iridessa.</prompt_response_5>
		<response_0_0>Somebody said I'm a worry wart? I'm not a worry wart!</response_0_0>
		<response_0_1>A worry wart is somebody who worries about every little thing, like whether or not the fireflies got lit right or if enough sunbeams got collected or if the rainbows have all the right colors or --</response_0_1>
		<response_0_2>Okay, I'm a worry wart.</response_0_2>
		<response_1_0>Why do I like sunflowers? You really have no idea?</response_1_0>
		<response_1_1>Because they look like the sun, of course! They're big and bright, and their yellow color is so -- soo -- YELLOW!</response_1_1>
		<response_1_2>I guess I like yellow, huh?</response_1_2>
		<response_2_0>I usually wear a yellow sunflower dress, but I have other pretty clothes, too.</response_2_0>
		<response_2_1>Tink gave me a cute orange Twirly Oak Top last season, and I made myself a really nice red Tulip Skirt just the other week.</response_2_1>
		<response_2_2>What I really need is a pair of warm boots for when I have to go to the winter meadows. I'd better go see Mendy about that.</response_2_2>
		<response_3_0>I love to light up fireflies. It's one of my favorite things to do!</response_3_0>
		<response_3_1>I remember when Tinker Bell tried to do it once. The fireflies chased her all over Pixie Hollow because she got a ball of light on her -- well, let's just say it didn't turn out well.</response_3_1>
		<response_4_0>We light-talents have an awful lot of responsibility, you know. </response_4_0>
		<response_4_1> I mean, nobody would be able to do ANYTHING without light, right?</response_4_1>
		<response_4_2>But believe it or not, I like darkness, too. I love to snuggle up in bed at night in the dark and dream! </response_4_2>
		<response_5_0>I've been thinking of changing my hairstyle. What do you think?</response_5_0>
		<response_5_1> Should I let my hair grow long? I'm not sure I would like having long hair.</response_5_1>
		<response_5_2>Naw, I think I'll keep my hair short the way it is. Long hair would be heavy, you know? And I like to keep things LIGHT! </response_5_2>
	</copy>
	<storyBoards>
		<storyBoard id="response_0">
			<line expressionId="2" >response_0_0</line>
			<line >response_0_1</line>
			<line >response_0_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_1">
			<line expressionId="1" >response_1_0</line>
			<line expressionId="1" >response_1_1</line>
			<line >response_1_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_2">
			<line expressionId="1" >response_2_0</line>
			<line >response_2_1</line>
			<line >response_2_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_3">
			<line expressionId="1" >response_3_0</line>
			<line >response_3_1</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_4">
			<line >response_4_0</line>
			<line >response_4_1</line>
			<line >response_4_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_5">
			<line >response_5_0</line>
			<line >response_5_1</line>
			<line >response_5_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
	</storyBoards>
	<otherStoryBoards>
	</otherStoryBoards>
</data>