<!--AUTOGENERATED THROUGH PYSCRIPTS FROM QUEST DOCS-->
<data>
	<copy>
		<prompt_response_0>Chat with Rosetta.</prompt_response_0>
		<prompt_response_1>Chat with Rosetta.</prompt_response_1>
		<prompt_response_2>Chat with Rosetta.</prompt_response_2>
		<prompt_response_3>Chat with Rosetta.</prompt_response_3>
		<prompt_response_4>Chat with Rosetta.</prompt_response_4>
		<prompt_response_5>Chat with Rosetta.</prompt_response_5>
		<response_0_0> Did you know I make perfumes, sugar? That's right, from flower petals of all kinds!</response_0_0>
		<response_0_1>Roses, daisies, pansies, lilies -- why, I even made perfume from a cactus flower once!</response_0_1>
		<response_0_2>Didn't like it. Smelled  sorta... prickly. </response_0_2>
		<response_1_0>My full name is Rosetta, but my friends sometimes call me Ro. </response_1_0>
		<response_1_1>And speaking of friends, you come visit me any time you want to! I'm usually right here in my garden! </response_1_1>
		<response_2_0>Let me give you a beauty tip, sugar -- always take care of your skin. You want to look good, don't you?</response_2_0>
		<response_2_1>I just love my rose beauty cream and my rose hand lotion and my rose moisturizer and --</response_2_1>
		<response_2_2>Hm. Guess I really like roses, huh? </response_2_2>
		<response_3_0>Did you know that Bess the art-talent painted my picture once? I have it hanging over my desk at home. It's absolutely beautiful!</response_3_0>
		<response_3_1>Not that I'm bragging. I mean, the PICTURE is beautiful. I mean, I think I look pretty good and all, but I was talking about the paintin' itself. I mean --</response_3_1>
		<response_3_2>Oh, never mind, sugar. I'm just gonna dig myself in a hole here. </response_3_2>
		<response_4_0>Hey, sugar, have you ever noticed that there are Lady Bugs but no Gentleman Bugs? Don't you think that's odd?</response_4_0>
		<response_4_1>There MUST be Gentleman Bugs somewhere!</response_4_1>
		<response_4_2>Iridessa likes to solve mysteries. Maybe she and I can get together some time and look for Gentlemen Bugs... </response_4_2>
		<response_5_0>Let's see here, I got my leaf clippers and my acorn shovel and my petal bucket and my waterin' can.</response_5_0>
		<response_5_1>I'm all set for a day in my garden!</response_5_1>
		<response_5_2>Oops! Forgot my lemongrass tea. I just can't garden without a nice tall glass of lemongrass tea, now can I? </response_5_2>
	</copy>
	<storyBoards>
		<storyBoard id="response_0">
			<line expressionId="1" >response_0_0</line>
			<line >response_0_1</line>
			<line >response_0_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_1">
			<line >response_1_0</line>
			<line expressionId="1" >response_1_1</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_2">
			<line >response_2_0</line>
			<line expressionId="1" >response_2_1</line>
			<line >response_2_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_3">
			<line >response_3_0</line>
			<line >response_3_1</line>
			<line >response_3_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_4">
			<line >response_4_0</line>
			<line >response_4_1</line>
			<line >response_4_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
		<storyBoard id="response_5">
			<line >response_5_0</line>
			<line >response_5_1</line>
			<line >response_5_2</line>
		</storyBoard>
	</storyBoards>
	<otherStoryBoards>
	</otherStoryBoards>
</data>