<page>
	<config>
		<tagline>
			<tagline align="center" font="pristina" yOffset="20">tagline</tagline>
		</tagline>
		
		<!--		
		<gamepolicies>
			<header icon_id="8">header</header>			
			<control>body1</control>
			<control>body2</control>
			<control>body3</control>
			<control>body4</control>
		</gamepolicies>
    --> 

		<gamepolicies>
			<header icon_id="8">body5</header>
			<header>body6</header>
			<knownissue>body7</knownissue>
		</gamepolicies>
		<gamepolicies>
			<header>body8</header>
			<knownissue>body9</knownissue>
		</gamepolicies>
		<gamepolicies>
			<header>body10</header>
			<knownissue>body11</knownissue>
		</gamepolicies>

    <!--

		<gamepolicies>
			<header icon_id="8">body12</header>
			<knownissue>body13</knownissue>
		</gamepolicies>

    -->

	<!--       Speak Mode is not an option it is now just whisper on and whisper off
		<gamepolicies>
			<header icon_id="8"><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">What is Speak Mode? How do I use it?</span>]]></header>
			<knownissue><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">When your Fairy is chatting in speak mode, everyone in the immediate area will hear her. Click on the <b>Speak icon</b> to the left of the chat bar to change it to the blue speak mode, and send your message. A chat bubble appears above your Fairy's head, which can be read by all surrounding Fairies.</span>]]></knownissue>
		</gamepolicies>
	-->

   <!--

		<gamepolicies>
			<header icon_id="8">body14</header>
			<knownissue>body15</knownissue>
		</gamepolicies>

  -->

	</config>
	
	<copy>
		<tagline><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">Page 2 - Game and Chat Policies</span>]]></tagline>
		<header><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">The Pixie Hollow Code of Conduct</span>]]></header>
		
		<body1><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">1. Always be kind and respect other Fairies. The Never Council does not tolerate any swearing, cheating, bullying, or any kind of mean behavior. Any Fairy who does not follow these rules while playing will be dealt with appropriately.<br><br></span>]]></body1>
		<body2><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">2. Never reveal any of your real world personal information. The best way to make sure you stay safe online is to NEVER share your real name, phone number, home address, e-mail, social networking site information, or pictures of yourself with ANYONE.  Also never exchange account information such as your member name or password with anyone under any circumstances.<br><br></span>]]></body2>
		<body3><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">3. Chat nicely with other Fairies. The Never Council will not permit talk about drugs, sex, race, or topics that may disturb other Fairies. Any Fairy who does not respect the peace of Pixie Hollow will be asked to leave the game.<br><br></span>]]></body3>
		<body4><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">4. No cheating. Any use of third party programs is not allowed. Fairies who use any third party programs while playing risk being permanently banned from the game.</span>]]></body4>
		<body5><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">What chat options do I have in Pixie Hollow? How do I use them?</span>]]></body5>
		
		<body6><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext"><TAB>SpeedChat</span>]]></body6>
		<body7><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext"><ul>
			<li>This is open to all Fairies. Chat away!
			<li>SpeedChat uses a set list of words and phrases that Fairies select from a drop-down menu.
			<li>To use SpeedChat phrases: Click on the Lightning Bolt icon to the left of the keyboard chat interface at the bottom of your screen, then click on the message you want from the SpeedChat drop-down menus. Every Fairy in the area will hear what you have to say unless you are chatting in Whisper mode. 
			
			</li></ul></span>]]></body7>
		
		<body8><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext"><TAB>SpeedChat Plus</span>]]></body8>
		<body9><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext"><ul>
			<li>This is open to all Fairies, but it can be turned off using Disney's <a href="http://disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/accountmanagement_pv.html">Parental Control</a> feature.
			<li>SpeedChat Plus is a keyboard chat system that uses a dictionary of Fairy-friendly words.
			<li>This chat setting lets Fairies chat with each other by typing words that are in the game's SpeedChat Plus dictionary. If you type in a word that is not in the dictionary, the word will flash in red and you'll have to change it before you can send your message.
			<li>This chat is filtered and moderated. Fairies can alert the Never Council of any bad behavior.
			</li></ul></span>]]></body9>
		<body10><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext"><TAB>Open Chat</span>]]></body10>
		<body11><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext"><ul>
			<li>This chat option is not currently offered in Pixie Hollow, but is available in other Disney Online products.</li></ul></span>]]></body11>
		<body12><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">Can I suggest words to add to the chat dictionary?</span>]]></body12>
		<body13><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">Of course! You can suggest a new word to us using the <a href="http://apps.disneyblast.go.com/cgi-bin/mail/generic_mail.cgi?template=pixiehollow/form.tpl&formId=chat">Contact Us</a> form. </span>]]></body13>
		<body14><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">What is Whisper Mode? How do I use it?</span>]]></body14>
		<body15><![CDATA[<span class="newsbodytext">Usually all Fairies in the meadow can see your messages.  Whisper mode allows your Fairy to speak directly with another Fairy - other Fairies will not see the conversation. Click on the <b>Whisper icon</b> to the left of the chat bar to change it to the green whisper mode, choose the Fairy you want to whisper to, and send your message. Instead of a chat bubble appearing above your Fairy's head, your whisper pal will see your message in the whisper log on the left side of their screen.</span>]]></body15>	
	</copy>
	
</page>