<!--AUTOGENERATED THROUGH PYSCRIPTS FROM EVOLUTION_CHALLENGES.XLS DOC-->
<EnemyAssets>
	<copy>
		<item19001>Truffle</item19001>
		<verb5_19001>Drag the rocks off the Truffle so they don't crush it!</verb5_19001>
		<verb4_19001>Click to help the Truffle outgrow the weeds!</verb4_19001>
		<verb0_19001>Drag the vines off the Truffle to untangle it!</verb0_19001>
		<verb6_19001>Shake the branch to hide the Truffle with falling leaves!</verb6_19001>
		<verb3_19001>Click on the water drops to clean mud off the Truffle!</verb3_19001>
		<verb7_19001>Move soil on top of the Truffle to protect it!</verb7_19001>
		<verb2_19001>Drag the fireflies on to the Truffle to keep it warm!</verb2_19001>
		<verb1_19001>Move the music notes onto the scared Truffle to calm it down!</verb1_19001>
		<desc19001>Truffle</desc19001>
		<item19002>Spider</item19002>
		<verb0_19002>Move the spider silk onto the Spider's web to fix it!</verb0_19002>
		<verb1_19002>Shake the scoop to sprinkle pixie dust to calm the nervous Spider!</verb1_19002>
		<verb6_19002>Shake the branch to hide the Spider with the falling leaves!</verb6_19002>
		<verb5_19002>Remove the web threads from the Spider!</verb5_19002>
		<verb7_19002>Click on the bandages to heal the Spider!</verb7_19002>
		<verb2_19002>Keep clicking on the sun to warm the Spider up!</verb2_19002>
		<verb3_19002>Drag the droplets onto the toad to splash it away from the Spider!</verb3_19002>
		<verb4_19002>Drag the leaves onto the web to grow a hiding place for the Spider!</verb4_19002>
		<desc19002>Spider</desc19002>
		<item19003>Firefly</item19003>
		<verb2_19003>Move the stars onto the Firefly to increase his glow!</verb2_19003>
		<verb7_19003>Remove the burs from the Firefly to cure his itchy wings! </verb7_19003>
		<verb6_19003>Click on the moths to distract them from the Firefly!</verb6_19003>
		<verb0_19003>Click on the wilting grass to fix the Firefly's home!</verb0_19003>
		<verb4_19003>Shake the honeycomb to drop honey to feed the Firefly!</verb4_19003>
		<verb5_19003>Click and drag the tangled ivy off the Firefly to free him!</verb5_19003>
		<verb3_19003>Drag droplets onto a bat to splash it away from the Firefly!</verb3_19003>
		<verb1_19003>Roll over the music notes to sing a calming song to the fearful Firefly!</verb1_19003>
		<desc19003>Firefly</desc19003>
		<item19004>Lizard</item19004>
		<verb1_19004>Click on the speech bubbles to warn the Lizard about dangers!</verb1_19004>
		<verb3_19004>Shake the raincloud to give the Lizard a bath!</verb3_19004>
		<verb2_19004>Drag sunshine onto the Lizard to keep her warm!</verb2_19004>
		<verb5_19004>Drag the raindrops into the leaf cup to get the Lizard a drink!</verb5_19004>
		<verb0_19004>Drag the twigs onto the twig nest to help build the Lizard a home!</verb0_19004>
		<verb4_19004>Keep clicking on the Lizard to help her grow bigger!</verb4_19004>
		<verb7_19004>Drag the leaves onto the Lizard to protect her from the cold!</verb7_19004>
		<verb6_19004>Click on the stinging wasps to protect the Lizard!</verb6_19004>
		<desc19004>Lizard</desc19004>
		<item19005>Butterfly</item19005>
		<verb0_19005>Drag the leaves onto the Butterfly to help her build a place to rest!</verb0_19005>
		<verb5_19005>Click on the Butterfly's friends to help them leave the Wilderness!</verb5_19005>
		<verb4_19005>Keep clicking the flower to grow the Butterfly a snack!</verb4_19005>
		<verb2_19005>Roll over the lanterns to guide the Butterfly out of the Wilderness!</verb2_19005>
		<verb6_19005>Shake the maracas to distract this prankster Butterfly!</verb6_19005>
		<verb1_19005>Roll over the arrows to give the Butterfly directions to a safe place!</verb1_19005>
		<verb7_19005>Drag the injuries off the Butterfly to heal her!</verb7_19005>
		<verb3_19005>Click on the dangerous fire ants to splash them away from the Butterfly!</verb3_19005>
		<desc19005>Butterfly</desc19005>
		<item19006>Bird</item19006>
		<verb3_19006>Drag water onto the muddy Bird to help wash him!</verb3_19006>
		<verb4_19006>Drag the twigs onto the nest to teach the Bird how to make a nest!</verb4_19006>
		<verb6_19006>Click the berries to lure the Bird out of the Wilderness!</verb6_19006>
		<verb5_19006>Roll over the arrows to guide the Bird to a safe tree to rest!</verb5_19006>
		<verb0_19006>Click the seeds to show the Bird how to crack them open!</verb0_19006>
		<verb7_19006>Drag the bandages onto the Bird to heal his sprained wing!</verb7_19006>
		<verb2_19006>Roll over to light the fireflies so the Bird can see in the dark!</verb2_19006>
		<verb1_19006>Click on the speech bubbles to tell the Bird how to avoid hawks!</verb1_19006>
		<desc19006>Bird</desc19006>
		<item19007>Squirrel</item19007>
		<verb7_19007>Click the thermometers until they are full to check on the sick Squirrel!</verb7_19007>
		<verb5_19007>Remove the thorns to save the Squirrel!</verb5_19007>
		<verb6_19007>Shake the branch to distract the Squirrel with acorns!</verb6_19007>
		<verb4_19007>Drag the acorns onto the pile to teach the Squirrel to store food!</verb4_19007>
		<verb0_19007>Drag the hammers onto the hut to help build the Squirrel's home!</verb0_19007>
		<verb1_19007>Click on the speech bubbles to tell the Squirrel how to avoid poison ivy!</verb1_19007>
		<verb3_19007>Click on the water vines to keep the Squirrel from getting stuck!</verb3_19007>
		<verb2_19007>Drag sunlight onto the Squirrel to warm her up!</verb2_19007>
		<desc19007>Squirrel</desc19007>
		<item19008>Frog</item19008>
		<verb1_19008>Roll over the frog prints to warn the Frog not to stray far from his pond!</verb1_19008>
		<verb3_19008>Shake the rainclouds to keep the Frog's skin wet!</verb3_19008>
		<verb4_19008>Keep clicking the lily pad to grow a new home for the Frog!</verb4_19008>
		<verb7_19008>Click on the flower cups to fill them with medicine for the sick Frog!</verb7_19008>
		<verb6_19008>Click on the speech bubbles to scare away dangerous animals!</verb6_19008>
		<verb2_19008>Click on the exclamations to illuminate the pond for dangers!</verb2_19008>
		<verb5_19008>Click on the leaves to collect them for a new sitting spot for the Frog!</verb5_19008>
		<verb0_19008>Drag the scissors onto the vines to help the Frog get unstuck!</verb0_19008>
		<desc19008>Frog</desc19008>
		<item23001>Monkey</item23001>
		<verb8_23001>Monkey Banana!</verb8_23001>
		<verb9_23001>Monkey Squeal!</verb9_23001>
		<verb4_23001>Monkey Grow!</verb4_23001>
		<verb2_23001>Monkey Illuminate!</verb2_23001>
		<verb3_23001>Monkey Splash!</verb3_23001>
		<verb6_23001>Monkey Distract!</verb6_23001>
		<verb5_23001>Monkey Move!</verb5_23001>
		<verb1_23001>Monkey Charm!</verb1_23001>
		<verb0_23001>Monkey Fix!</verb0_23001>
		<verb7_23001>Monkey Heal!</verb7_23001>
		<desc23001>Monkey</desc23001>
	</copy>
</EnemyAssets>
