<panel>
	<swfs>
		<swf type="content">{panelContent}/convertItem.swf</swf>
		<swf type="code">{panelCode}/convertItem.swf</swf>
	</swfs>
	<copy>
		<oops target="notEnough.header">Oops!</oops>
		<buy target="notEnough.buy.caption">OK</buy>
		<learnMore><![CDATA[<u>Learn More</u>]]></learnMore>
		<notEnoughMessageSingular>You need #AMOUNT# more Pixie Diamond to Upgrade this Member item into a Diamond Item.</notEnoughMessageSingular>
		<notEnoughMessagePlural>You need #AMOUNT# more Pixie Diamonds to Upgrade this Member item into a Diamond Item.</notEnoughMessagePlural>
		<notEnoughAnimalMessageSingular>You need #AMOUNT# more Pixie Diamond to Upgrade this Animal Friend into a Diamond Friend.</notEnoughAnimalMessageSingular>
		<notEnoughAnimalMessagePlural>You need #AMOUNT# more Pixie Diamonds to Upgrade this Animal Friend into a Diamond Friend.</notEnoughAnimalMessagePlural>
		<checking>Just Checking...</checking>
		<messageChecking>Would you like to Upgrade this Members Only item into a Diamond Item?</messageChecking>
		<messageCheckingAnimal>Would you like to Upgrade your Animal Friend into a Diamond Animal Friend?</messageCheckingAnimal>
		<cost>#COST# Pixie Diamonds</cost>
		<diamondItemHeader>Upgrade to a Diamond Item!</diamondItemHeader>
		<yes>Yes</yes>
		<no>No</no>
		<convert target="convertAlert.convert.caption">Upgrade</convert>
		<cancel>Cancel</cancel>
		<ok>OK</ok>
		<youGotIt>Upgrade Complete!</youGotIt>
		<messageWardrobe>Your upgrade with Pixie Diamonds is complete! You can find your clothes in your Leaf Journal. Would you like to wear this item now?</messageWardrobe>
		<messageWardrobeNoWear>Your upgrade with Pixie Diamonds is complete! You can find your clothes in your Leaf Journal.</messageWardrobeNoWear>
		<messageStorage>Your upgrade with Pixie Diamonds is complete! You can find your item in your Leaf Journal.</messageStorage>
		<messageAnimal>Your upgrade with Pixie Diamonds is complete! Your can now interact with your Animal Friend.</messageAnimal>
		<convertAlertAnimalMessage>This is a Members Only friend. You can Upgrade it to a Diamond Friend and care for it without membership!</convertAlertAnimalMessage>
		<convertAlertItemMessage>This is a Members Only item. You can Upgrade it to a Diamond Item and use it without membership!</convertAlertItemMessage>
	</copy>
</panel>
