<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<copy><![CDATA[
	<span class="header">
		<p>
			Getting Started
		<br>
	</span>
	<span class="title">
			1.	What&apos;s a Clickables&#x2122;?
		<br>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
			Clickables is a new technology that allows toys to connect to PixieHollow.com.  A Clickables sensor allows information to be exchanged when connected to another.
		<br>
		</p>
	</span>
	
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			2.	How do I start using my Clickables toy?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			In your internet browser, enter the following address: <a href="http://pixiehollow.go.com/clickables.html">http://pixiehollow.go.com/clickables.html</a> and click on the Download Clickables button.  Follow the setup instructions to install the application.  If clicking the link does not work, copy and paste it into your web browser.   PLEASE DO NOT PLUG IN YOUR TOY UNTIL YOU HAVE DOWNLOADED AND INSTALLED THE APPLICATION TO YOUR DESKTOP.	 
		<br>
		</p>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			3.	What are the minimum system requirements for the Clickables Application?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			<li>
				Windows Vista/XP/2000 operating system
			</li>
			<li>
				800 MHz processor (1.4 GHz recommended)
			</li>
			<li>
				256 MB RAM (512 MB recommended)
			</li>
			<li>
				100 MB free hard disk space
			</li>
			<li>
				USB port
			</li>
			<li>
				Keyboard and mouse
			</li>
			<li>
				Broadband Internet connection  (350K or faster) 
			</li>
			PLEASE NOTE - CLICKABLES CURRENTLY IS NOT MAC COMPATIBLE. 
		<br>
		</p>
	</span>	 

	<span class="title">
		<p>
			4.	Do I need a Disney account?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Yes.  You need a Disney account. You can log in using your Account ID and Password you created on any of the Disney family of sites. If you do not have an account, go to <a href="http://pixiehollow.go.com">http://pixiehollow.go.com</a> and sign up for one.   It&apos;s free.	 
		<br>
		</p>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			5.	Can I use my Pirates Online or Toontown account?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Yes, you can log in using your Pirates Online or Toontown account, but if it&apos;s the first time you log in to Pixie Hollow, you will need to create a Fairy first.	 
		<br>
		</p>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			6.	Do I need a paid subscription to pixiehollow.go.com to use Clickables toys?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			No.  You can access all the toys online content without a subscription.
		<br>
		</p>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			7.	Once I set up my Clickables toy, can I change the Disney account it works with?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			No, once you assigned your Disney account ID to the toy, you cannot change it. But, you can change the Fairy you assign to your Clickables as often as you&apos;d like.
		<br>
		</p>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			8.	What happens if I plug in multiple Clickables items such as a Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet and a Jewelry Box at the same time?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Each toy that is connected to the computer will show up on the screen and then you can select which Clickables toy you want to play with first.  However, for a faster online experience, it&apos;s preferable to only plug in one toy at a time.
		<br>
		</p>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			9.	Who do I contact if I have trouble with my toy or the program?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Please contact us by email at clickables@pixiehollow.com.
		<br>
		<br>
		<br>
		</p>
	</span>
	
		
	<span class="header">
			Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet<br>
	</span>
	<span class="title">
			1.	What can my Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet do?<br>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Your bracelet allows you to share the magic of PixieHollow with your friends offline. Once you set-up your bracelet, it can exchange a friendship invitation, message and online gift with any other Clickables Fairy Friendship bracelet it touches.
			</span>
		</p><br>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				You can also touch Clickables Fairy Charms to the bracelet and unlock the charm&apos;s online gift.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Or you can transfer Tink Points from the Clickables Fairy Game by touching the game to your bracelet.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			2.	How do I setup my Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet the first time?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			You must set-up your bracelet before you can connect the bracelet with other Clickables toys.
		</p>
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Download and install the Clickables application found at pixiehollow.go.com/clickables.html.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Once the download and installation is complete, an icon will appear on your desktop.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Then, attach your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet to your computer with the supplied USB cable.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			d.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				The Clickables application should open automatically when the USB is connected.  If it does not open automatically, double click the desktop icon to launch the application. 
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			e.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Click Set Up Bracelet.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			f.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If you are not logged in to your Disney Account, you will have to do so.  If you don&apos;t have one, you will need to follow the instructions to create one.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			g.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Select the Fairy you want to use with your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			h.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Pick a message you want your friend to see.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			i.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				There are 5 SpeedChat phrases that come with your bracelet.  Your Fairy can use these in PixieHollow.com and give them to friends.  Pick the gift of a SpeedChat phrase you want to give your friend.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			j.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Finally, you will need to confirm that you want to match the Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet to your account. Once you confirm, your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet will always be tied to that account.  You can change the Fairy on your account that is associated with the Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet, but not the account.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>
			3.	How do I connect with other Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelets?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Press the activation button on your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet.  The Fairy Friendship Bracelet will flash once.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Touch the Clickable sensor <img src="http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/images/y.png" hspace="4" vspace="4"/><br> to the sensor on top of your friend&apos;s Fairy Friendship Bracelet.  Make sure the top two circles of the <img src="http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/images/y.png" hspace="4" vspace="4"/><br>touch each other.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				When you see the light flash, you and your friend have exchanged message, gift and friendship invitations.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
	
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			4.	I touched my bracelet to my friend&apos;s bracelet but it didn&apos;t light up.  What&apos;s wrong?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Before you touch bracelets, you must press the activation button first.  Please press the activation button every time before you touch bracelets.  Also, make sure the top two circles of the<img src="http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/images/y.png" hspace="4" vspace="4"/><br>touch each other to ensure connection.  If you made a proper connection and saw a solid light instead of the flashing light, one of the bracelets is full and must be connected online to make space for more friendship connections.
		</p>
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Attach your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet to your computer with the provided USB cable.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If your Clickables application is not open or does not open automatically when you plug in your Fairy Friendship Bracelet, open it by double clicking on the desktop icon.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If you have multiple devices plugged in choose the Fairy Friendship Bracelet from the menu screen.  Select Add Friends in the main menu.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			d.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Select the Friendship image.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			e.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				It will open a popup message.  Select the &quot;Let&apos;s be Friends&quot; button to accept the friendship.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			f.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Confirm your selection.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			g.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Your new friendship will appear in your Friends Lists in Pixie Hollow once the friend has also accepted your friendship invitation.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
	
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			5.	What&apos;s a SpeedChat phrase gift?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Every time you click bracelets with a friend, you will receive a SpeedChat phrase as a gift together with the friendship exchange.  The SpeedChat Phrase will allow you to talk with other Fairies by pointing and clicking from a preset menu of chat phrases in Pixie Hollow.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			6.	I see Fairies using different SpeedChat phrases that did not come with my bracelet.  How do I get those?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Each bracelet comes with 5 different SpeedChat phrases to use and give friends.  In total there are 30 different Fairy SpeedChat phrases.  To collect them all, connect your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet with different friends.  You can use any of the SpeedChat phrases you collect in Pixie Hollow, but you can only send the 5 that came with your bracelet as gifts to your friends.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			7.	How do I change the Fairy, gift, and message stored on my Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Plug in your Fairy Friendship Bracelet and log in to the Clickables application.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Choose the Change Bracelet button from the menu screen.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				You can change the Fairy assigned to your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet, the gift that Fairy shares with other Fairies, and message your friends will receive. Click OK button to save your changes.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>
			8.	Can I send a friendship invitation without a message or SpeedChat phrase gift?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			No.  You must pick a message and a SpeedChat phrase to share with your Fairy friends.   If your friend already has the SpeedChat phrase, Fairies will let her know.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>
			9.	How do I connect Clickables Fairy Charms to my Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Press the activation button on your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet.  The Fairy Friendship Bracelet will flash once.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Touch the back of the charm to the Clickable sensor to the <img src="http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/images/y.png" width="11" height="10" hspace="4" vspace="4"/><br>on the top of your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet.  Make sure the top two circles of the <img src="http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/images/y.png" width="11" height="10" hspace="4" vspace="4"/><br>touch each other.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				When you see the light flash, your charm has been transferred to the bracelet.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
	
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			10.	How do I unlock the charm&apos;s online item?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Attach your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet to your computer with the provided USB cable.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If your Clickables application is not open or does not open automatically when you plug in your Fairy Friendship Bracelet, open it by double clicking on the desktop icon.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If you have multiple devices plugged in, choose the Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet from the menu screen.  Select Add Charms in the main menu.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			d.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Select the Fairy you want to receive the charms.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			e.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Select the charms that you want to give to your Fairy.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			f.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Confirm your selection.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			g.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				The charm&apos;s online item is waiting for your Fairy in her Leaf Journal in Pixie Hollow. 
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>
			11.	How do I use my Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet to receive Tink Points?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Press the activation button on your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Touch the Clickables Fairy Game to the sensor <img src="http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/images/y.png" hspace="4" vspace="4"/><br> on the top of your Fairy Friendship Bracelet.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				When you see the Fairy Friendship Bracelet flash, the Tink Points have been transferred off the game and onto the bracelet.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>
			12.	How do I transfer my Tink points online?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Attach your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet to your computer with the provided USB cable.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If your Clickables application is not open or does not open automatically when you plug in your Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet, open it by double clicking on the desktop icon.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If you have multiple devices plugged in, choose the Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet from the menu screen. 
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			d.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Click on the Deposit Tink Points button in the menu.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			e.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Select a Fairy to receive the Tink Points.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			f.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Confirm your selection.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			g.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				 The Fairy Tink Points balance is now updated and the points are no longer on your bracelet.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
 
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			13.	What can I use my Tink Points for?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			You can use Tink Points for a butterfly to fly with you in your home and the meadows of Pixie Hollow. 
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
	
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			14.	How much can be stored on my Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet at a time?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			You can touch your bracelet to 30 other Clickables, either charms, friendships or Tink Points.  After 30, the bracelet needs to be connected online to make more space and then it can connect with more Clickables. 
		</p>
		<p>
			If you press the activation button, connect a Clickable and your bracelet does not flash, but displays a solid light, the bracelet is full.  Please connect it online. 
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>
			15.	Is there a limit to the number of Clickables I can connect with my bracelet?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			No, you can use your bracelet an infinite number of times, so click away! The bracelet can only hold 30 at one time, so you will need to connect it online periodically.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>
			16.	How do I change the battery in my bracelet?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				To use your bracelet away from the computer, please install 1 Lithium (CR2430) battery.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Unscrew the battery cover with a Phillips screwdriver.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Insert 1 Lithium battery with the positive (+) and negative (-) ends facing the proper direction as indicated in the battery compartment.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			d.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Replace the cover.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
		<br>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="header">
			Friends Questions<br>
	</span>
	<span class="title">
			1.	Can I decline friendship invitations after I have touched Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelets?<br>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Yes, when reviewing your Friendship invitations you can choose to Accept Friendship or Decline Friendship.<br>
		</p>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			2.	Can I cancel a friendship after it has been accepted?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Yes, to remove a friendship, log into Pixie Hollow and click on your Friends List. Select the name of the Fairy whose friendship you want to break and remove them by selecting the broken heart in their profile.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			3.	What bonuses do I receive for accepting friendships?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			When you accept friendship invitations, your Fairy will receive a special badge in the Leaf Journal in Pixie Hollow.  You will earn a badge when you accept 5 friendship invitations.  You will earn another badge when you accept 25 friendships invitations.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
	
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			4.	How many friends can I have?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			There is a limit of 300 friends in Pixie Hollow. 
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			5.	What happens if my Friends List is full?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			If your Friends List is full, you will not be able to accept new Friendship invitations in the Clickables application. You will receive a message asking you to remove friends before you can add new friendships. To make more space in your Friends List, log into Pixie Hollow and click on your Friends List, select the name of the Fairy whose friendship you want to break and remove them by selecting the broken heart in their profile. 
		</p>
		<br>
		<br>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="header">
		<p>
			Clickables Jewelry Box
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="title">	
			1.	What can my Clickables Jewelry Box do?<br>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Your Clickables Fairy Jewelry Box can unlock Clickables Fairy Charms, receive Tink Points from a Clickables Fairy Game and store your jewelry.<br>
		</p>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>
			2.	How do I set up my Jewelry Box?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If the Clickables application is not installed yet, go to <a href="http://pixiehollow.go.com/clickables.html">http://pixiehollow.go.com/clickables.html</a> to download and install to get started.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Plug in your Jewelry Box to your computer with the supplied USB cable.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Click Setup Jewelry Box button.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			d.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				When you confirm setup of the Jewelry Box, it will be tied to your Pixie Hollow account
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			3.	How do I connect Clickables Fairy Charms with my Clickables Jewelry Box?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Press the activation button on your Jewelry Box.  The Jewelry Box will light up.   Now, touch the back of the charm to the Clickable sensor <img src="http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/images/y.png" hspace="4" vspace="4"/><br>to the <img src="http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/images/y.png" hspace="4" vspace="4"/><br>on the top of your Jewelry Box.  Make sure the top two circles of the <img src="http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/images/y.png" hspace="4" vspace="4"/><br>touch each other.  When you hear the sound of Pixie Dust and see the light flash, your charm has been stored.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				To add another charm, press the activation button. The Jewelry Box will light up.   Now, touch the back of the charm to the Clickables sensor on the Jewelry Box.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>
			4.	Can I connect with Clickables Fairy Charms when the Jewelry Box is not connected online?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Yes, but you will need to connect the Jewelry Box to the computer and use the Clickables application to unlock the charms.  To use your Jewelry Box away from the computer, please install 3 AAA batteries.
		</p>
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Unscrew the battery cover with a Phillips screwdriver.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Insert 3 AAA batteries with the positive (+) and negative (-) ends facing the proper direction as indicated in the battery compartment.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Replace the cover.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
	
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			5.	I touched a Clickables Charm to the Jewelry Box but the music did not play.
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Before you touch your Clickables charm to the Jewelry Box, you must press the activation button.  Please press the activation button every time before you add a charm. Also, make sure the top two circles of the <img src="http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/images/y.png" hspace="4" vspace="4"/><br>touch each other.  If your Jewelry Box lights up, but music did not play, the Jewelry Box is full and needs to be connected online before storing more Clickables.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
	
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			6.	How do I unlock charms online?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Attach your Jewelry Box to your computer with the provided USB cable.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If your Clickables application is not open or does not open automatically when you plug in your Jewelry Box, open it by double clicking on the desktop icon.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If you have multiple devices plugged in, choose the Jewelry Box from the screen.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			d.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Select Add Charms from the menu.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			e.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Choose the Fairy and which item you are giving to that Fairy.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			f.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				The online item is waiting for your Fairy in her Leaf Journal in Pixie Hollow.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			7.	What if I try to unlock a Charm I already have 
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			If you already have the item, you will be notified when you try to give that charm to the individual Fairy.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			8.	Can I touch my Clickables Fairy Game to my Clickables Jewelry Box?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Yes.  Press the activation button on your Jewelry Box.  Then connect the <img src="http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/images/y.png" hspace="4" vspace="4"/><br>on your Clickables Fairy Game to the Jewelry Box.  When you hear the music, the Tink Points have been transferred from the Game to your Jewelry Box.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			9.	Can I touch my Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet to my Clickables Jewelry Box?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			No.  To exchange friendships, you must connect two Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelets together.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			10.	How many Clickables can my Jewelry Box store?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Your Jewelry Box can hold 30 Clickables, either charms or connections to the Clickables Fairy Game, before it needs to be connected online.  After downloading online, you can continue to connect with more Clickables.
		</p>
		<br>
		<br>
		<br>
	</span>

		
	<span class="header">
		<p>
			Charms Questions
		<br>
	</span>
	<span class="title">
			1.	Can I share my charms with my friends?<br>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
    <p>
			Go for it! Share your charms with your friends by touching the <img src="http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/images/y.png" hspace="4" vspace="4"/><br>to her Jewelry Box or Friendship Bracelet.  Now you both have the online item for your Fairy.<br>
    </p>
	</span>
	
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			2.	How long will it take for my charm item to show up in my inventory in Pixie Hollow?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			It is almost immediate.  After you unlock your charm item using the Clickables application, log in to Pixie Hollow and you will see your online item in your Leaf Journal.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			3.	How can I give a charm to all my Fairies?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Select Add Charms using the application and pick the Fairy you want to receive charms.   Repeat the step by selecting Add Charms again and pick another Fairy you want to receive charms.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			4.	How many charms can I collect?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			You can purchase 31 charms at your local retailers.  Charms are sold in the Clickables Fairy Charms Starter Set, Clickables Fairy Charm Bracelets and Clickables Fairy Charm Sets.  To see the full collection, <a href="http://pixiehollow.go.com/clickables.html">click here.</a>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			5.	What are the online rewards I receive for collecting charms?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			By collecting charms, your Fairy will receive special badges in her Leaf Journal in pixiehollow.go.com.  Collect all the charms, and you will earn a special badge you can show off to your friends in Pixie Hollow.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			6.	Where can I get charms?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Look for them at local retail stores.
		</p>
		<br>
		<br>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="header">
		<p>Clickables Fairy Game Questions</p>
	</span>
	<span class="title">
			1.	 How can I use my Clickables Fairy  Game for items in Pixie Hollow?<br>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Playing games earns you Tink points that can be used to redeem a butterfly. Your butterfly will fly with you around in Pixie Hollow for a limited amount of time.<br>
		</p>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>
			2.	How do I setup my Clickables Fairy Game?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If the Clickables application is not installed yet, go to <a href="http://pixiehollow.go.com/clickables.html">http://pixiehollow.go.com/clickables.html</a> to download and install to get started.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Attach your Clickables Fairy Game to your computer with the provided USB cable.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If your Clickables application is not open or does not open automatically when you plug in your Clickables Fairy game, open it by double clicking on the desktop icon.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			d.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If you have multiple devices plugged in, choose Clickables Fairy Game in the screen.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			e.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				In the main menu screen, select Set Up Game.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			f.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				When you confirm setup of the Clickables Fairy Game, it will be tied to your account.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
	
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			3.	How do I play the individual games to earn Tink Points?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			To find out how to play all the individual games, <a href="event:http://a.disney.go.com/fairies/pixiehollow/pdfs/clickables_fairy_game.pdf">click here</a>.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			4.	How can I share Tink Points with friends? 
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			If you want to share your Tink Points with friends, touch your game onto her Clickables Fairy Friendship Bracelet.   The total balance in your bank will be given to your friend.  Remember, once you have connected with a friend, the points are removed from your Game and only your friend will receive the amount online.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			5.	Are there any limits to the amount of points I can earn or give to friends?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			No, you can give as many points to your friends at any time you want.  The Game holds 99,990 points and then will need to be connected online before you can earn more.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			6.	How do I redeem my Tink points for a butterfly?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			You can redeem Tink points for a butterfly with the Tink points in your Fairy account by choosing the Redeem Tink Points in the main menu.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			7.	How do I print out my Fairy to display in the cover?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Go to <a href="http://pixiehollow.go.com/clickables.html">http://pixiehollow.go.com/clickables.html</a> and select the Print Fairy Portrait.  Your Fairy image will be printed at the correct size to fit in the Game&apos;s cover.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>
			8.	How do I replace the batteries in my Game? 
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Your Game comes with 3 AAA batteries.  To replace, please:
		</p>
		<p>
			<li>
				Unscrew the battery cover with a Phillips screwdriver.
			</li>
			<li>
				Insert 3 AAA batteries with the positive (+) and negative (-) ends facing proper direction as indicated in the battery compartment.
			</li>
			<li>
				Replace the cover.
			</li>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			9.	My game screen froze.  How can I fix it?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Please push the reset button on the back of the game with a blunt instrument.
		</p>
		<br>
		<br>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="header">
		<p>
			Butterfly Questions
    </p>
	</span>
	<span class="title">
    1.	What is a butterfly for?<br>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
    <p>Butterflies are Fairies' friends who fly with you in Pixie Hollow for a limited amount of time.  Your butterfly will be with your Fairy in Fairy homes and all public meadows.  They will not appear in &quot;special&quot; areas like games, crafting areas or shops.<br></p>
	</span>
	<span class="title">
		<p>
			2.	How do I get a butterfly?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			a.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Attach your Clickables Fairy Game to your computer with the provided USB cable.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			b.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If your Clickables application is not open or does not open automatically when you plug in your Jewelry Box, open it by double clicking on the desktop icon.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			c.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				If you have multiple devices plugged in, choose the Game from the screen. 
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			d.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Select Redeem Tink Points from the main menu.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			e.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Choose the Fairy you want to have the butterfly.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			f.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Choose which butterfly you would like.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			g.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Click Next.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			h.
			<span class="letterPoint">
				Click OK on the congratulations screen.
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			i.
			<span class="letterPoint">
					Your butterfly will fly with you the next time you go to Pixie Hollow.
			</span>
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			3.	Can I have more than one butterfly at a time?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			No, each Fairy can only have one butterfly at a time.  If you want to change your butterfly, you can use your Tink Points to replace the butterfly you currently have.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>

	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			4.	Does the time I am logged out count as time with my butterfly?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Yes, butterfly time is counted based on calendar time regardless of whether you are in Pixie Hollow or not.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			5.	What happens to my Fairy if I choose another butterfly Friend before my current butterfly leaves?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			If you choose the same butterfly, your time will be extended. If you choose a different butterfly then the one you just selected will replace your current butterfly.
		</p>
		<br>
	</span>
		
	<span class="title">
		<p>	
			6.	I can&apos;t see my butterfly flying with me, even though I have time left.  Where is it?
		</p>
	</span>
	<span class="body">
		<p>
			Your butterfly is visible in the Fairy homes and all public meadows.  They will not appear in "special" areas like games, crafting areas or shops because the Fairy will not fly around in those areas.
		</p>
		<br>
		<br>
		<br>
		<br>
		<br>
		<br>
		<br>
	</span>	
]]></copy>